JIADAI K SUNG Brooklyn, NY

646.944.1844 | Jiadai.sung.tech@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/jiadai-sung

SUMMARY

10 years of work experience in hospitality sector, responsible for addressing customer needs and ensuring they have a positive experience with the business. Now transitioning into IT industry, I am eager to apply my skills and enthusiasm for problem-solving in the technology-oriented settings. Self-driven, actively pursuing IT Certifications for personal growth.

SKILLS

Problem Solving & troubleshooting Active listening & communication Customer Service Time Management

SOFTWARE

Microsoft Office 365 Point of Sale (POS) Systems Shopkeep & Revel

LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

ENGLISH Bilingual proficiency

MANDARIN Bilingual proficiency

CANTONESE Full professional proficiency

WORK EXPERIENCE

Shift Manager | Kung Fu Tea Manhattan, NY 2018 - PRESENT

- Implement and maintain Revel iPad (POS) Systems.
- Provide technical support related to Mobile apps technical glitches.
- Coordinate with Marketing Team to address, promote and oversee store operation.
- Handle escalated customers who may need assistance and problem solving.

Operations Manager | Langkawi Restaurant Brooklyn, NY 2017 - 2018

- Setup Google-Fi mobile virtual network operator (MVNO) service and Google Wi-Fi.
- Supervised day-to-day operation, recorded daily sales, and administered payroll.
- Coordinated and directed the tax filing with an accountant.
- Managed staffs to achieve optimum workflow and effectiveness.

Floor Manager | HanGawi Manhattan, NY 2012 - 2016

- Worked closely with reservation to optimize table turnover.
- Addressed any problems or customer concerns appropriately.
- provided support to shift members and coordinated team activities.

EDUCATION

A.A Criminal Justice | Borough of Manhattan Community College, NY 2016 - 2018

CERTIFICATIONS

CompTIA A+ Certificate | CompTIA Google IT Support Certificate | Coursera Google Data Analytics Certificate | Coursera

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Member & Owner | Windsor Terrace Food Coop Brooklyn, NY

- Perform transaction with Shopkeep iPad Systems (POS).
- Balance transactions at end-of-day report for inventory management purpose.
- Help resolve issues for customers with a product and service.
- Ensure WiFi connectivity and quick resolution of network problems.